天坠之战的三百年后
合成、时间轴：鱼呀鱼呀鱼
嗯.....
Mm-mmm.
你还活着
You're alive.
你梦到了什么  小天使
What are you dreaming, little angel?
好吧
Well...
试一下
Try again.
目前只能做到这种地步
Well, that's the best I can do for now.
真是太谢谢了
I'm really grateful, Doc.
我下周会多加班的
I'll be getting some overtime next week.
好，等你有钱再说吧
Yeah, pay me when you can.
给  我特地带的
Here, I got these for you.
我老婆在22号农场干活
My wife works out at Farm 22.
谢谢
Thank you.
我改天再来
See you next time.
再这样
Keep getting paid in fruit,
我们就要自己去摘橙子了
and we'll be picking these ourselves.
你好  瞌睡虫
Hello, sleepyhead.
你好
Hi.
感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
还好
Okay.
有哪里疼吗
Any pain anywhere?
没有
No.
- 麻木呢- 没有
- Numbness? - No.
有活动不便吗
Motor dysfunction?
我有点饿了
I'm a little hungry.
快吃吧
Eat this.
能提高血糖含量
Get your sugar levels up.
味觉感受器运转正常
Taste receptors are working.
谢谢
Thank you.
把皮剥了你会发现这个其实很好吃
You'll like this a whole lot better with the peel off.
我不想太冒昧
I don't mean to be rude...
但我们认识吗
but am I supposed to know you?
其实...
Actually...
我们从未见过
we haven't met.
我是戴森.依德医生   这是格哈德护士
I'm Dr. Dyson Ido. This is Nurse Gerhad.
你们知道我是谁吗
And do you know who I am?
好吧  我们还希望你..
Well, we were hoping...
能告诉我们
you'd fill in that part.
因为你的身体进行了完全替换
Since you're a total replacement cyborg...
你以前的躯体大部分都坏掉了
and most of your cyber body was destroyed...
我们找不到任何记录
we can't find any records.
但你拥有的人类大脑却奇迹般的保存了下来
But your very human brain was miraculously intact.
理论上  你应该记得点什么
Theoretically, you should remember something.
是吗
Oh. Well...
它基本上是空白的
It's still pretty blank.
不   应该说完全一片空白
No, it's completely blank, actually.
我连名字都忘记了
I don't even know my own name.
我们看看好的一面
Let's look at the bright side.
眼泪功能完好
Your tears are working.
嗯...
Mmm.
太好吃了
That's so good.
这个叫什么
What do you call this?
那是什么
Yeow! What's that?
- 撒冷- 噢!
- Zalem. - Oh!
它是最后一座天空城
The last of the great sky cities.
- 它怎么能飘   魔法吗- 不
- What holds it up? Magic? - No.
比魔法还厉害   工业科技
Something stronger. Engineering.
它下面就是我们的钢铁城
And down here, we have Iron City.
也算别有风味吧
With all its charm.
戴森.依德医生    是你吗
Dr. Dyson Ido. That's you.
我在学着记名字  给我起一个吧
While I'm learning names, do you have one for me?
阿丽塔
Alita.
是个好名字
It's a nice name.
我喜欢
I love it.
我能留着吗
Can I keep it?
至少等我想起自己的名字
At least until I can remember my real name?
- 好的- 谢谢
- Mm-hmm. - Thank you.
好了
Okay.
- 你想到处逛逛吗- 当然
- Do you want to take a look? - Yes.
为什么这里这么多种语言
Why are there so many languages?
在我提到的大战之后
Um, after the big war I told you about...
天坠
The Fall.
天坠之战后  只有撒冷保存了下来
After The Fall, only Zalem was left...
世界各地的幸存者于是剧集于此
and survivors came here from all over the world.
下面的人为撒冷工作
Everybody down here works for Zalem.
工厂也好   农场也好
The Factory, the Farms...
有人去过撒冷吗
Does anyone ever go up to Zalem?
去看看吧
We should go.
下面的人不到上面去
Nobody from down here ever goes up.
这是从未被打破的铁则
It's a rule that's never broken.
怎么了
What?
这一击重摔下手真狠
Oh! And he takes him down hard!
那是什么
What is that?
机动球
It's Motorball.
真是太酷了
That's so cool.
不是什么值得你去看的东西
Nothing you need to be wasting your time watching.
阿丽塔
Alita.
等我一会
One minute, please.
你好
Hi.
你好啊
Hello.
想来点吗
You want some?
快吃吧
Here you go.
我能抱你吗
Can I hug you?
快点让开
Step aside.
不要挡路
Out of the way.
你太牛了
Outstanding.
你走路不长眼睛吗
Why don't you watch where you're going?
长见识了
I gotta admit...
从来没有人敢挑战百夫长
I never saw anybody challenge a Centurion before.
哇  你好沉
Whoa. You're heavy.
我意思是
I mean...
哇
Oh.
你是改造人
You're a cyborg.
抱歉   我很喜欢你的手
Sorry, I was just admiring your hand.
介意吗
Can I see?
哇
Wow.
手艺真不错
It's really nice work.
依德医生做的吗
Did Doc Ido do it?
全身都是他造的
He built all of me.
除了核心   那是我的
Except my core. That's mine.
做工太棒了
Well, he did a really great job.
刚那个到底是什么
Hey, what are those things?
百夫长
The Centurions?
你是哪个星球来的
What planet are you from?
依德在废铁场找到我的
Ido found me in the Scrapyard.
废铁场
- The Scrapyard? - Mm-hmm.
那意味着
But that would mean...
医生
Hey, Doc.
我搞到了你想要的驱动板
I got those driver-boards you were looking for.
阿丽塔刚来这里
Alita is new here.
她还在熟悉环境
She's still learning about things.
我得走了
I gotta go.
晚点给你送去
I'll drop those off later.
有个四方伺服器要重建
I need a rebuild on a quad servo.
有空再聊
Maybe I'll see you around.
他是谁
Who is that?
雨果
Hugo.
是个勤奋的小伙子  不过
He's a hard worker, but...
阿丽塔  来吧 我们走
Alita, come on, let's go home.
-雨果-回家吧
- Hugo. - Let's go home.
啊
There's the damn Jackers
那个该死的掠夺者把我撕碎的时候
that ripped me to shreds standing right there.
在旁边看热闹的百夫长指头都没动一下
And that vale madre Centurion wouldn't lift a finger.
为什么有人抢你的胳膊和腿
Why would anyone wanna take your arms and legs?
扭矩耦合器
Torque coupling.
掠夺者想把你的零件拿到黑市去
Those Jackers want your parts for the black market.
好提供给机动球比赛
To supply the Motorball games.
你很走运
You were lucky.
昨晚另外一个女孩儿就死在附近
Another girl was murdered last night, right near there.
对   我听说了那家伙
Yeah, I heard that guy carves girls up...
把女孩的身体肢解之后拿去卖了
and sells their body parts.
抱歉   医生
Sorry, Doc.
这段时间你不要天黑后出去
For now, I don't want you out after dark.
明白吗
Is that understood?
知道了
Okay.
如果你白天出去
And if you go out during the day,
也不要跑到太远的地方
don't wander too far from this neighborhood.
好吧
Okay.
要保证
Promise?
我保证
I promise.
孩子
Hey, kid.
你这人怎么回事
Hey, what's your problem?
她是谁
Who's the girl?
我的新助手
My new assistant.
她用了你女儿的身体我很惊讶
I was surprised to see her in our daughter's body.
你不是很多年前就想毁掉吗
You were supposed to have destroyed that years ago.
- 我做不到- 很明显
- I couldn't. - Clearly.
你告诉过她那具身体是谁吗
And did you tell her who you built that body for?
我们的女儿死了   依莲
Our daughter is dead, Chiren.
你得放手了
- You need to let it go. - Oh.
念念不忘的人显然不是我
It's obviously not me that's clinging to something here.
到这来
Over here!
- 雨果- 阿丽塔
- Hugo. - Hey, Alita.
这就是机动球吗
Is this Motorball?
只是争球游戏
It's just a scrimmage.
想一起玩吗
Do you wanna join in?
来吧，大家都玩机动球
Come on, every kid's gotta play Motorball.
好  我加入
Sure, why not?
我想和你再次合作
I want us to be a team again.
我有了新的实验室
I have a great new setup...
还有设备
and equipment...
配得上你的技术
worthy of your skills.
我们合力
Together, we can build the finest champions
可以打造出游戏史上最强大的选手
this game has ever seen.
可以帮我回家
Could be my ticket home.
你什么时候才能明白根本回不去了
When are you going to realize there is no way back?
不要白日做梦了
It just does not happen.
维克托能办到
Vector can make it happen.
你竟然还相信维克托
I can't believe you trust Vector.
他和高层有联系
He has very high connections.
我不会帮你制造怪物的
I won't help you build monsters.
我一定要回到撒冷去
I'm going to get back to Zalem somehow.
就算用手爬回去我也在所不惜
I'll claw my way there with my bare hands if I have to.
朋友们   这是阿丽塔
Hey, everyone, this is Alita.
嗨
Hi.
实战就是最好的学习
Best way to learn is to go in.
快快  快点传球
Pass the ball!
就是这样
That's it.
转弯时屈身寻找空挡
Lean into your turns, look for an opening.
我找到感觉了
I think I'm getting it!
放开控制器吧
You can let go of the remote now.
见鬼
Oh, crap.
挡住她啊
- Come on, get her! - Come on, get her!
动作快点   把她截住
Cut her off!
可有米  快点传球
Koyomi, pass her the ball.
她接住了  接住了
And she got it! She got it!
拦住她
Get her!
抱歉  小公主
Sorry, princess.
你也太棒了
Nice, Tanji, thanks.
她从来没玩过
She's never played before.
抱歉
Sorry.
接住了
Got this!
给我
Mine!
别想碰到我
You got me!
真棒
Good shot.
你的怪胎女朋友是不是坏了
Your freak girlfriend's got some serious malfunctions.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
她让你出了这么大丑
She humiliated you so severely.
好了  我们今晚见
All right, I'll see you tonight.
还有  她不是我女朋友
And, uh, she's not my girlfriend.
随便吧
Whatever.
你玩这个很有天赋啊
You've got some talent for this game.
我得回家了
I've got to get home now.
依德让我天黑之前回去
Ido wants me in the house before dark.
我送你吧
Do you want a ride?
你什么都想不起来了
So you can't remember anything?
我正在努力想呢
I'm trying to.
家人  朋友   喜欢的食物
Family, friends, favorite food?
不知道   也许是橙子吧
Nothing. Well, maybe oranges.
我是昨天吃到的
But that's just since yesterday.
橙子
- Oranges? - Uh-huh.
不行   无法接受
Nope. Unacceptable.
我带你开开眼
Here, check this out.
感谢你的惠顾
Thank you very much, Senora.
给你   拿好了
And here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
准备好了吗
You ready?
尝尝这个
Try this.
相信我
Trust me.
这是巧克力
It's chocolate.
嗯..
Mmm.
- 这也太好吃了- 不错吧
- That is so great. - It's good, right?
我有喜欢的食物了
I have a favorite food now.
- 多谢- 这是我最喜欢的了
- Thank you. - This is my favorite food.
我可不觉得
Well, I wouldn't call it that.
我觉得
I would.
看啊   看那个人
Hey, look. Check it out.
他是猎人勇士
It's a Hunter-Warrior.
是个赏金猎人    名叫扎潘
He's a bounty hunter. Named Zapan.
他在寻找目标
Scanning for his mark.
我可不想被他追杀
I wouldn't wanna be that guy.
快看他的刀
Look at that sword.
钢铁城不允许居民持枪
All guns are outlawed in Iron City.
有枪可是死罪
Punishable by death.
不能对撒冷有威胁
Anything that challenges Zalem.
我不是告诉你天黑之前回家的吗
Didn't I tell you to be home before dark?
有什么关系  我就是忘记时间了
What's the big deal? I just lost track of time.
好吧   不要相信任何人
Yeah. Don't trust anyone.
这里的人对同胞并不友好
People do terrible things to each other here.
你的手臂怎么了
What happened to your arm?
给  吃了吧
Here, eat this.
没事吧
You okay?
你的大脑需要丰富的营养
You still need proper nourishment for your brain.
你有巧克力吗
You have any chocolate?
这个世界很残酷
It's a harsh world.
人们习惯弱肉强食
The strong prey on the weak down here.
你要坚持自己的梦想
You gotta stay focused on your dream.
你的梦想呢
What's your dream?
我带你看
I'll show you.
这是我的秘密基地
This is my secret place.
这儿的风景最棒
Best view in town.
哇
Wow.
这太酷了
Really cool.
不   你看
No. Look.
那里
That view.
噢.
Oh.
好吧
Right.
我想知道上面是什么样
I wonder what it's like up there.
总比下面的垃圾场好
Better than this dump down here.
快听
Listen.
这是工场的货物被送上了撒冷
It's stuff from the Factory going up to Zalem.
但是管道只能送货   不能走人
But the tubes are just for cargo, not for people.
如果我像你一样强
If I was as strong as you,
我现在就顺着管道爬上去
I'd climb that tube to Zalem right now.
他们不允许任何人上去
They don't let anybody up there.
他们希望你这么想
Yeah, that's what they want you to think.
你要认识对的人
You just gotta know the right people.
- 我恰好就认识一个- 真的
- I happen to be connected. - Oh.
你必须愿意做出牺牲
You gotta be willing to do what it takes.
不管付出多少
Whatever it takes.
其实你见过上面
Funny thing is, you've seen it.
你只是想不起来
You just can't remember.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
医生在废铁场发现了你
Doc found you in the Scrapyard.
那里所有东西都是从撒冷扔下来的
All that stuff is dumped from Zalem.
所以你肯定是从上面来的
So you must be from up there.
我猜是吧
I guess so.
真希望你能说说上面的事
If you could just tell me what those eyes have seen.
我也很希望
I wish I could.
我一直努力回忆
I keep trying to remember, but...
但依旧是一片空白
It's still a blank.
我想我可能是不那么重要
I'm starting to feel like I wasn't very important.
只是个跟垃圾一起扔下来的
Just an insignificant girl
不起眼的女孩
thrown out with the rest of the garbage.
- 不  快住手- 阿丽塔
- No! Stop! - Alita!
不要这么做
Don't do it!
不好
Oh, no.
这是个陷阱
It's a trap.
你在找我吗   医生
Looking for me, Doctor?
或许该叫你猎人勇士
Or should I say, Hunter-Warrior?
猎人勇士
"Hunter-Warrior"?
这下糟了
Oh, no.
看来我们被他发现了
Looks like he's got us.
别乱跑
Don't move.
谢谢你把这个女孩带来
Hey, thanks for bringing a girl.
这可给我们省了不少时间
That's gonna save us some time.
打得不错   作为人类说
Nice shot, for a Meat-Boy.
不
No!
你是来救我的是吗
You came to rescue me?
你真是太贴心了
That is so sweet.
你的眼睛真好看
You have nice eyes.
他是我的   那个女孩归你
He's mine. You can have the girl.
我要他的眼睛就行
So long as I get his eyes.
阿丽塔  快跑
Alita, run!
我的天啊
My God.
撕了那个小跳蚤
Rip that flea!
你真是太美丽了
You are so beautiful.
我要把你撕开看看里面是不是跟其他人一样
I wanna rip you open and see if you're ugly inside.
那么的丑陋
Like the others.
看着她死
Watch her die.
来吧  小跳蚤
Come here, little flea...
让我把你的脑袋拧下来
so I can pinch your head off.
啊~!
Hi-yah!
99!
注意你左边
On your left!
啊~!
Hi-yah!
我绕不了你  小跳蚤
You'll pay, little flea.
格鲁依什卡有仇必报
Grewishka does not forget.
我会来找你们
I'm coming for you.
两个
Both.
格鲁依什卡有仇必报
Grewishka does not forget!
战斗的时候  我想起来些什么
When I was fighting, I remembered something.
我参加过一场大战
I was in a huge battle.
你吓到我了
You surprised me.
你也很让我惊讶
Well, you surprised me, too.
天坠之战前
Before The Fall...
有警察来制止犯罪活动
there were police to stop criminals.
现在由工厂出钱让我们干这些脏活
Now, the Factory pays us to do the dirty work.
这里是猎人勇士 17739.
Hunter-Warrior 17739.
真的是猎人勇士
You are a Hunter-Warrior.
留在这儿
You stay here.
不要去杀人
Don't kill anyone.
改造人尼西亚的悬赏金额是2万元
Bounty for the cyborg Nyssiana was 20,000 credits.
你应该告诉我这些事
You should've told me who you really are.
你是为了赚钱吗
And do you do it for the money?
我确实拿了钱
I take the money.
否则诊所很多年前就关门了
Otherwise the clinic would've closed long ago.
我不想解释
I do this work for other reasons
我做这个的真实原因
I'd rather not talk about.
你必须解释一下
You have to talk about it.
战斗触发了我的记忆
Something during the fight triggered a memory.
我在月球上
I was on the moon.
你隐瞒了关于我的事情
You know more about me than you're saying.
我这副身体是谁的
Whose body is this?
我是谁
Who am I?
这是你的女儿
This was your daughter?
这身体是为她制造的
You built this body for her?
他名字叫阿丽塔
Her name was Alita.
她曾做梦
She was really looking forward to waking up
想拥有一双奔跑的腿
with legs that could run.
所以你为她做了敏捷的腿
You built her a pair of fast legs.
她还没有机会用
She never got to use them.
她就被害了
She was murdered.
发生了什么
What happened?
我的一个病人突然大半夜跑来诊所
A patient of mine came to the clinic one night,
找药
looking for drugs.
我曾经是机动球装备调试师
I was a tuner for the Motorball games...
我为他打造了一副拥有强大力量的机械身体
and I had made a machine body for him of obscene strength.
他就是回来惩罚我罪孽的恶魔
He was my demon, coming back to me.
你在这干什么
Hey! What are you doing there?
阿丽塔没有办法及时躲开
Alita couldn't get out of the way fast enough.
她的妈妈  依莲
Her mother, Chiren,
接受不了女儿的死
couldn't deal with Alita's death.
或许她只是不想面对我
Maybe she just couldn't deal with me.
于是我成了猎人
So I went hunting.
我必须要杀了他
I needed to kill him.
或许我也期待他能杀了我
Maybe I was just hoping that he would kill me.
我任然无法平静
It brought no peace.
还有很多恶魔逍遥法外
There were other demons like him out there...
我总是觉得这一切的责任都在我
and I felt, somehow, I was responsible for all of them.
所以我注册成为猎人勇士
So I registered as a Hunter-Warrior.
这不是什么光彩的事
There's nothing noble about it.
你找到平静了吗
Did you ever find peace?
我找到了你
I found you.
我不是你女儿
I'm not your daughter.
我甚至不知道我是谁
I don't know what I am.
好吧
I do.
来看看你的改造核心
Have a look at your original Cyber-core.
这就是你的大脑
This is your brain.
一个健康的普通年轻女孩的大脑
A normal healthy teenage girl's brain.
真有这东西吗
If there is such a thing.
但是看看你的心脏
But this is your heart.
你核心的一部分
Part of your original core...
它是由一个反物质威信反应堆驱动的
powered by an Anti-Matter Micro-Reactor.
看来我的心脏很强
So I've got a strong heart?
你的心脏
You have a heart strong enough
强大到足以驱动这座钢铁城很多年
to power all of Iron City for years.
这是失传的科技
This is lost technology.
没人能造的出这东西
Nobody's made this stuff since...
天坠之战后
before The Fall.
好吧
Yeah, right.
所以我至少有300岁
So I'm 300 years old?
亲爱的  没错
Sweetheart, you are.
我不想让我的选手在比赛中失败
I don't want my players losing unless I tell them to.
这不能靠运气
It can't be left to chance.
你承诺给我冠军
You promised me champions.
你也承诺给我最好的一切
And you promised me the best of everything.
我让你找的军用驱动器呢
Get those military servos I asked for.
我看你根本不想赢
You don't have a winning attitude.
先准备明天的比赛吧
Just be ready for tomorrow's game.
救救我
Help me.
格鲁依什卡
Grewishka?
我为什么要花时间救你
Why should I waste my talent on you?
你看她干的好事
Look what she's done to me.
依德的机器人小丫头
Ido's little cyber girl.
你说什么
What did you say?
记忆中的女儿叫我99号
The woman in my memory called me 99.
你看到的是你过去生活的一瞬间
What you saw was a flash of your previous life.
我是谁
Who was I?
你总会想起来的
In time, you'll remember.
我要把她撕扯两半
I wanna rip her in half.
格鲁依什卡
Grewishka.
真是日落西山啊
Oh, how the mighty have fallen.
要回收他的零件吗
Are we stripping him for parts?
你来看看这个
I need you to look at something.
这是监控芯片  刚刚发现
It's a Telepresence Chip. He's wired.
有人在撒冷控制他
Somebody in Zalem is riding him.
整座钢铁城到处都藏着眼线
There are watchers behind the eyes all over the city.
这太平常了
Pretty common now.
重建他的时候
I'd just as soon remove it...
我会把那东西取下来
while I'm rebuilding him.
你为什么
Why are you wasting time
要再这个混混身上浪费时间
on this burnt-out street junk?
有点个人原因
It's a personal matter.
你喜欢你的工作吗  维克托
Do you like your job, Vector?
如果你喜欢名望
If you like your position
还有顺带的各种便利
and the many comforts that come with it...
我建议你听依莲医生的话
I strongly suggest you listen to Dr. Chiren.
诺瓦
Nova.
恕我冒犯
My apologies.
是谁伤了格鲁依什卡
Who did this to Grewishka?
一个改造人女孩
A little cyborg girl.
伤口处
Though the impact points
有强大力量冲击的痕迹
are evidence of extraordinary power...
我不明白
I don't understand how she could create
那么瘦小的身躯怎么有那等力量
such force with such a small body.
这种强大的力量并非来自她的身体
It was not the power of the body that did this.
而是来自内心
It was the mind.
他懂得一种战斗技术叫做机甲术
She knows the fighting techniques of Panzer Kunst.
把格鲁依什卡修好
Rebuild Grewishka.
让他把女孩带给我
Have him bring her to me.
尸体
Dead.
他走了
He's gone.
还没走
Not gone.
是重建了
Repatched.
你是个聪明人  医生
You're a clever woman, Doctor.
而且愿意不惜代价达成目的
And determined to reach your goal at any cost.
所以我给你的任务
So I'll make you this offer.
如果你能够令我满意
If and when you have pleased me...
我会让你实现你的愿望
I will grant you the destiny you seek.
撒冷
Zalem.
你能送我回撒冷
You'll send me to Zalem?
我就在撒冷
I'm there right now.
我愿意为您倾尽全力
Consider my services engaged.
没人悬赏格鲁依什卡
There is no bounty on Grewishka.
你都向工厂举报了
But you reported it to the Factory.
他杀了那么多女人
Him killing all of those women...
有人在保护他
Somebody's protecting him.
谁有那么大的权力
Who has the power to do that?
肯定是高高在上的人
Someone far beyond us here.
我们最近还是少出门
We better stay off the street for now.
我想像你一样成为猎人勇士
I wanna be a Hunter-Warrior like you.
阿丽塔  不要胡闹了
Alita, that's impossible.
我们可以合作
We could be a team.
这是危险又见不得人的工作
Alita, this is dangerous, dirty work.
- 我知道- 你不知道
- I know. - No, you don't.
你不能替我做决定
How is that your choice to make?
这没得商量
It's out of the question.
我可能在生死危机的关头
I might need a life-or-death situation
才能找回记忆
to remember who I was.
哪怕只有短短一瞬间
Even if it's just for a second.
阿丽塔  有些事情还是忘掉好
Alita, some things are better left forgotten.
我不希望你的双手染血
I don't want blood on these hands, too.
那我自己想办法
Then I'll find out for myself.
阿丽塔
Alita.
我真是受够了
I'm just tired of it.
他只想让我当他的乖女儿而已
He just wants me to be his perfect little girl.
那你要听他的   还是听你自己的
So, you gonna live by his rules or yours?
多精彩的大战
What a battle!
他们两个一整场都在互相缠斗
These two have been going at each other all match.
这才是机动球
Welcome to Motorball.
加修纲拿到了球
Jashugan has got the ball.
克莱默进攻了
Claymore attacks!
加修纲击倒了他
Jashugan takes him out!
马萨克斯把加修纲打飞了
Masakus sends Jashugan flying!
亚加卡帝拿到了球  得到一分
Kutty now with the ball, one point.
扎里基紧追不舍
Zariki is in hot pursuit.
- 扎里基出局- 哇哦!
- Wipeout, Zariki! - Whoo!
亚加卡帝像布娃娃一样被扔出去
And he throws Kutty like a rag doll!
来吧   我带你去个地方
Come on. Let me show you something.
我认识这里所有人
I know all the pit crews and tuners.
我给你介绍下
I'll introduce you around.
谁是最厉害的?
Who's the top player?
我觉得加修纲
Right now, I'd say Jashugan
最有可能获得最终冠军
has the best chance of making Final Champion.
左边车轮的倾角有问题
Camber's still off in the left bogie.
第六弯转向过度了
I was oversteering in turn six.
最终冠军是什么
What's Final Champion?
是选手们的最高荣誉
It's the best thing a Motorball player can win.
每隔几年都会选出一个王牌选手
Every few years, they choose a player that can't be beaten...
可以前往撒冷
and he gets to go to Zalem.
雨果
Hey, Hugo.
流畅就是稳   稳就是快
Slow is smooth, smooth is fast.
一次搞定  不要出错
Do it once, do it right.
装甲车马上进站维修
Juggernaut needs to pit, right now.
你们想赢吗
Do you like to lose?
那就把它喊进来
Then get him in here.
克莱默已经重建了  他怎么不参赛
Claymore is a rebuild. Why is he not tracking?
阿丽塔在这儿
Alita's here.
那是维克托
That's Vector.
机动球大赛的负责人
He basically runs Motorball.
我们和他有很多往来
We do a lot of business with his team.
他的新调试师需求很多
Selling parts to him and his new tuner.
依莲
Chiren.
兄弟们  快点把我送回去
Let's go, guys. Come on, get me back out there.
怎么  又不是只有你认识人
What? You're not the only one with connections.
亚加卡帝追上了装甲车
Kutty closing in on Juggernaut.
基努巴也锁定了亚加卡帝
Kinuba has Kutty in his sights.
基努巴用爪镰
Oh! Kinuba went through him
轻而易举击垮了他
like laundry with those Grindcutters.
那个武器没违规吗
Is that weapon even legal?
基努巴德新武器太强了
Kinuba's too strong with that new weapon.
会影响赔率
He's screwing up the odds.
你知道吗
You know...
我正好用得上他的爪镰
I could really use his Grindcutters...
去做另一个项目
for our other project.
真红疾风在人群中脱颖而出
Crimson Wind making her way through the field.
你觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
我喜欢
I like it.
雨果  赶快走吧
Yo, Hugo. We gotta go.
我有点事情
Hey, something's come up.
- 你要去哪- 我有事要处理
- Where are you going? - I just gotta do something.
你能自己回去吗
Can you get back okay?
没问题
Yeah, sure.
你明天有空吗
Can you go out tomorrow?
我想带你
I wanna show you this place me and Tanji know.
去破败之地那边看看
It's out in the Badlands.
也许能找回记忆
It might help with your memory.
我很愿意去
I'd appreciate that.
谢谢
Thanks.
你做的一切
For everything.
他真是太棒了  他就是赢家
Wow! He is throwing down!
Whoo!
见鬼
Oh, shit!
- 怎么搞得?- 见鬼
- What the hell? - Shit.
快点儿
Hurry up!
你们死定了
You're dead!
你们这群畜生
You little runts!
我要碾碎你们的脑袋
I'm gonna smash your skulls!
你们居然敢这样
You can't do this to me!
- 好了- 给我
- Ready. - Give me.
小心
Careful.
你们这些混蛋
You street punks!
我饶不了你们
I'm gonna make you pay for this.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
感谢你的团队
Compliments to your crew.
多谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
交给我吧
I'll pass it on.
哥们
Hey, man, where's my cut?
我那份呢
Hey, when you gonna tell your hardbody
你什么时候告诉她这事
you jack cyborgs, huh?
我不会说
I'm not.
你别说漏了
And neither are you.
你担心她会甩了你吗
You afraid she's gonna cut you loose?
把他扔出去  把爪镰送给依莲
Get the Grindcutters over to Chiren right away.
走工作通道
Use the service gate.
去吧
Go.
维克托  你这混蛋
Vector, you prick.
我早该想到的
I should've known.
你早该想到的是
What you should've known, my friend...
没有任何人
is that no one...
比大赛更重要
is greater than the game.
城市外面有什么
What's outside the city?
没有什么
Not much.
战争
The war wiped out all utilities
几乎毁掉了所有东西
and most everything else.
我们只知道
All we know is the sky cities fell all in one night...
一夜之间天空之城全都毁灭了
when the enemy launched the last attack
敌人触动了所有飞船发起了总攻
with every ship they had.
敌人是谁
Who was the enemy?
火联
The URM.
火星联盟共和国   简称火联
United Republics of Mars. The U-R-M.
火联
URM.
在战争的最后一夜
On that last night of the war...
大地颤栗  天空燃烧
the earth shook and the sky burned.
到了早上  撒冷还在空中
But in the morning, Zalem still stood.
前面就到了
It's just up ahead.
这艘船来自撒冷大战
This ship is from the battle of Zalem.
也许这些战争时期的东西
I figured that maybe seeing stuff
能帮到你
from the war would help trigger your...
拾荒者们
Salvagers have jacked some stuff
搜刮走了不少金属物件
over the years for metal...
但因为是火联的技术
but it's all URM technology,
所以保存完好
so it's mostly been left alone.
- 这是火联的船- 没错.
- This is an URM ship? - Uh-huh.
因为没人搞得清这玩意
You know, it's pretty hard to sell this stuff
所以很难卖得出去
since no one knows what it is...
嘘
Shh!
我们得去船舱
We have to go to the command deck.
就在前面
It's forward.
她怎么知道的
How does she know that?
我们都过不去   都在水下
Hey, we can't get there. It's underwater.
你觉得她能憋多久
How long do you think she can hold her breath?
不知道
I don't know.
这是要搞事啊
Oh, this can't be good.
别想了
Forget it.
我不会做的
I won't do it.
但
But...
但你必须帮我
But you have to.
它能击败格鲁依什卡
This would help us fight Grewishka
还有其他被派来的杀手
and anyone else he sends after us.
这副身体
This body...
拥有我需要的力量
it has the power I need.
我感受到了难以言喻的联系
I feel a connection to it I can't explain.
这可能是本来的我
This could be who I am.
你得到一个从头再来的机会
You've been given a chance to start over,
一个新的人生
with a clean slate.
有多少人有这样的机遇
How many of us get that?
为什么那样一搜敌舰
Why did an enemy warship...
会回应我呢
respond to me?
因为我认得它
Because I knew that ship.
我曾经乘坐过一样的飞船
I've been on others like it, haven't I?
对不对
Haven't I?
不管以前如何  都不是现在的你
Ouf, whatever you were, it's not who you are now.
不
No!
我是个勇士   对吗
I'm a warrior, aren't I?
你知道的
And you know.
你一直都知道的
You've always known.
这是狂战士装甲
This is called a Berserker.
是火联科学会开发的人形武器系统
It's a humanoid weapon-system created by the URM Technarchy.
你的核心
Your core
就是用来驱动这样的身体的
was designed to interface with this type of body.
你的身份证识别码启动了它
Your identity code activated it.
你这与生俱来的战斗技术
The instinctive fighting technique you use...
被称为机甲术   是供机甲使用的失传格斗术
is Panzer Kunst, a lost combat art for machine bodies.
是狂战士们用的
It was used by the Berserkers.
这就是为什么你会被争斗所吸引
This is why you're drawn to conflict without hesitation.
这是你训练的一部分
It's part of your training.
你并不仅仅是勇士  阿丽塔
You are not just a warrior, Alita.
你是名火联狂战士
You're an URM Berserker,
是我们历史上最先进的一种战斗机甲
the most advanced cyborg weapon ever created.
这也正是我拒绝帮你
And that is exactly why
与这副身体结合的原因
I will never unite you with this body.
没关系
That's fine.
很好
Fine.
说出你的目的
State your business.
我是来注册成为猎人勇士的
I'm here to register as a Hunter-Warrior.
顺利吗
How'd it go?
你成为猎人勇士了
You're a Hunter-Warrior, all right.
医生要气死了
Doc's gonna be pissed.
我要听他的吗
Whose rules do I live by?
你确定要进去吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Are you sure about this?
这是赏金猎人的地盘
This place is just for bounty hunters, nobody else...
你以为这是什么
What do you think this is?
再说了  依德也觉得我喜欢惹麻烦
Besides, Ido says I'm drawn to conflict.
我记得你
Oh. I remember you.
你还好吗  小家伙
How's it going, little guy?
不错
Good?
你来掩护我吧
Just watch my back.
天啊
Oh, boy.
扎潘  别把桌椅打坏
Hey, Zapan! Not the furniture.
来这干嘛  小美人
What brings you in here, sweets?
想见识下猎人的风采吗
Come to see the Hunters up close?
不完全是
Not exactly.
小甜心也是赏金猎人
Cupcake here is a bounty hunter.
哈哈哈
What?
所以说你以为
So, you went down,
填好了赏金猎人表
you filled out your application forms...
拿到了身份徽章
you got your ID badge...
你就和我们一样了吗
and now you're just like us, yeah?
给你介绍下
Let me introduce you
你的职业同僚们
to some of your professional colleagues.
这位是白热掌大师克莱夫.李
This is Master Clive Lee of the White Hot Palm.
他有超过200次的击杀记录
He has over 200 confirmed kills.
207次
207.
这位是螺丝头
Well, and this is Screwhead,
最致命的赏金猎人之一
one of our most lethal bounty hunters.
还有训狗师麦克蒂格
And then, there's McTeague...
你看他的猎犬  全部都忠心耿耿
the Dogmaster, with his Hellhounds.
他最大的毛病  是找不到足够的证据
His biggest problem is having enough left to identify after,
去兑换赏金
so he can collect the bounty.
然后是我
And then, there's me.
扎潘
Zapan.
大马士革钢刀 的拥有者
Keeper of the legendary Damascus Blade.
精心打磨的单分子刀刃可以削铁如泥
Honed to a monomolecular edge. It slices armor like butter.
天坠之战前由失传的火联冶金技术锻造
Forged before The Fall by the lost arts of URM metallurgy.
你杀了谁才搞到的
And who did you kill to acquire it?
猎人勇士都是独行 的孤狼
A Hunter-Warrior is a solitary predator.
你要是想和我们争夺目标
You'll be competing against us for the kill.
要先弄清你的对手
You can see what you're up against.
谢谢
Thanks.
我是来请你们帮忙的
I came to ask for your help...
去对付共同的敌人  格鲁依什卡
against our common enemy, Grewishka.
他被这个系统所保护
He's being protected by the system,
可以毫无顾忌地肆意破坏
and continues to rampage unchecked.
他要来追啥依德和我
And now, he's after Ido and me.
所以我呼吁大家
So I'm calling on you...
我的猎人勇士兄弟们
my Hunter-Warrior brothers.
让我们联合起来
Let's band together
为了钢铁城的所有人
and defeat him once and for all.
有人接受吗
Any takers? Hmm?
没有吧
No?
真让我意外
Big surprise.
我通常不会照顾新人
You know, normally, I wouldn't take a rookie under my wing...
比如分享经验
share my knowledge.
但是为了你我可以破例
I'm willing to make an exception in your case...
如果你踹了那边的人类
if you'll cut loose Meat-Boy over here
我就请你喝一杯
and let me buy you a drink.
说话小心点
Hey, watch it.
那么我从你这个话痨绣花枕头身上
And what could I learn from a loudmouth pretty boy...
能学到什么经验呢
who spends all of his money on his face?
也许我把你胳膊腿都卸了
Maybe I'll pull your arms and legs off,
把你的头在街上滚一圈
roll your head around in the street.
你就知道什么是礼貌了
Maybe that'll teach you some manners.
小心你的发型
You might mess up your hair.
这下太丢人了 扎潘
You gonna take that, Zapan?
这个有好戏看了
He's scared of the pretty girl.
啊
Aah!
你配不上这把武器
You do not deserve such a weapon.
我听说你们是钢铁城的英雄
I heard you were the heroes of Iron City.
看来只是浪得虚名
I am not impressed.
你要做什么
What the hell are you doing?
我希望你能退后一点
I'm gonna need you to stand way back.
我接受在座所有人的挑战
I will take on anyone in this room.
如果我赢了
And if I win...
你们就跟我并肩战斗
you fight alongside me.
你打坏了我的鼻子
This bitch broke my nose.
是我打的
Yes, I did.
还英雄呢
Heroes?
我只看到了垃圾场的混混  各种改造废物
All I see are junkyard punks, assorted cyber-trash...
还有一群过气的机动球选手
and a bunch of drunken Motorball burnouts
慢的没资格参赛
too slow to play the game.
谢谢 雨果
Thanks, Hugo.
我的天
Oh, no.
都住手
Hold it!
别闹了
Knock it off!
否则我不免费修
Or no more free repairs!
我跟她一起的
I'm with her.
真是对不住了
Sorry about this.
我们必须好好谈谈了
You and I are going to have a little talk.
我们已经谈过了
No, we had our talk.
是你让我别无选择
You didn't leave me another choice.
不要动
Don't move.
是格鲁依什卡
It's Grewishka.
他这是怎么了
What's happened to him?
这就是给你的回答
Well, to answer your question...
我搞了一点小升级
I've had a little upgrade.
我是来找那个女孩的
I'm only here for the girl.
她是你的了
Ah, she's all yours.
你们坐视不管吗
What about the rest of you?
这个家伙没有悬赏   医生
There ain't no bounty on this guy, Doc.
不关我们的事
Not our problem.
没关系的  依德
It's all right, Ido.
哇.
Aw.
唯一有勇气的是条狗
The only one with courage.
你也太天真了
So innocent.
天真的人不配在钢铁城  你这个小跳蚤
Iron City is no place for innocents, little flea.
面对邪恶  我不能袖手旁观
I do not stand by in the presence of evil.
来我的世界找我
Come to my world.
下来啊 小跳蚤
Come, little flea.
别去  阿丽塔
Alita! No!
欢迎来到地下世界  我的世界
Welcome to the underworld. My world.
从这往上是一层又一层的世界
From here, there are worlds above worlds above worlds...
一直到你能想象的最高处
going farther up than you can imagine.
每一层的垃圾都会掉到下一层
And the trash of each one flows down to the one below...
最终汇聚到这里
'til it all ends up here.
这就是我曾经的居所
It's where I used to live.
也将成为你的葬身之所
And it's where you're going to die.
跳舞吧  小跳蚤
Dance, little flea.
我被遗忘在这力糜烂
I was forgotten here to rot.
但我被拯救了
But I was saved...
获得了重生
remade...
拯救我的人此刻也掌握着你的命运
by the same hand that shapes your destiny even now.
他是谁
Whose hand?
我的主人  诺瓦
My master, Nova.
关于我  你都知道什么
What do you know about me?
你  有用幸存者的灵魂
You have the soul of a survivor.
永远不要放弃
You'll never give up.
Aah.
要善于发现
Know what is hidden.
记得问自己
Always ask...
有什么是自己没看到的
what is it that you are not seeing?
诺瓦？
Nova?
他是必须要被除掉的恶龙
He is the dragon that must be slain.
再来
Again.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
还往哪儿跑
Where are you going?
怎么了啊
What's the matter?
我的小玩具不想继续玩了吗
My little toy doesn't want to play anymore?
我要把你变成活体项链
I'll turn you into a living pendant
就挂在我的胸前
to adorn my chest.
这样我就可以每时每刻都听到
Then I can hear your voice every moment of the day...
你求饶的哭喊
pleading for mercy!
Hi-yah!
去你的求饶
Fuck your mercy.
不
No!
快回来
Break off!
他可不喜欢狗  我讨厌他
He wasn't a dog lover. I hate that.
过来  宝贝
Oh, come on.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你以为这样就可以摆脱过去吗
You think you can replace us that easily?
无论救活她多少次都是徒劳
Bring her back as many times as you like.
没有任何人敢来伤害你了
No one will dare harm you again.
这个就是狂战士身体的适应技术
It's the adaptive technology of the Berserker body.
躯体正在潜意识的
The shell is reconfiguring
自我认知重塑形象
to her subconscious image of herself.
我从未见过这样的
I've never seen anything like it.
现在这个身体的每个系统都在进行微调
It's making micro-adjustments throughout every system.
看来她比你想的年纪还大
Looks like she's a little older than you thought.
快瞧瞧你啊
Well, look at you.
你说的很对
Well, you were right.
勇士就应该配备勇士的身体
A warrior's spirit needs a warrior's body.
它可以吸收空气  产生弧形等离子火焰
It draws in air, generating an arc plasma...
至于你怎么控制  我就不清楚了
but how you control it, I don't know.
毕竟也没附带使用说明  对吧
Didn't exactly come with a manual, did you?
算是某种武器吧
It's some kind of weapon.
现在知道自己是谁了
Now you know who you are.
不过这只是个躯体
But that's just a shell.
躯体是不分好坏的
It's not bad or good.
一切都取决于你
That part's up to you.
看看这个
Check these out.
挺新鲜的  对吧
Pretty fresh, right?
阿丽塔
Alita!
哇
Wow.
你
You're...
- 我复原了- 简直是完好无损
- Back together? - Very back together.
你看上去
You look...
不一样了
different.
这都是纳米技术
It's all nanotech.
是连依德都搞不懂的技术
It's a bunch of stuff even Ido hasn't figured out yet.
你比之前更强了
So are you stronger than you were?
当然  也更快了
Yeah. And faster, too.
这感觉
It feels...
更像我
more me.
不少人
You know, some guys might be
会被你这样的女孩吓跑的
intimidated by a girl like you.
真的吗    为什么
Really? Why is that?
因为你能把他们的胳膊卸下来
'Cause you could rip my arm off
然后揍他们
and beat me with the wet end.
好吧   可别惹我
Well, then, don't piss me off.
你为什么不喜欢她
Why don't you like her?
我就是接受不了那种机器身体
I just never got the whole hardbody thing.
而且她是火联来的
And besides, she's URM.
总有一天她会成为我们的敌人
It means she was probably the enemy at one point.
是啊  300年前的事
Yeah, 300 years ago.
差不多得了
Get over it.
我的触觉也更灵敏了
I'm a lot more touch sensitive, too.
而且有了更高密度的力量反馈
A lot higher density of force feedback and...
和材质感应器
texture sensors.
想试试吗
You wanna try it?
能感觉到吗
You can feel this?
可以
Yes.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
这样呢
How about this?
也能
Yes.
我在哪儿
Where am I now?
你
You're...
在我身边
with me.
你会困扰吗
Does it bother you...
我不是一个完整的人
that I'm not completely human?
你是我见过的人里最具人性的一个
You are the most human person I have ever met.
他不让我修好眼镜
He won't even let me fix his eye.
他想记住疼痛
He says he wants the pain.
够了
Enough.
诺瓦
Nova.
你又失败了
You have failed me.
站起来
Stand.
除非你了解她否则永远无法战胜她
You will never triumph until you understand what she is.
她是狂战士幸存者
She's the last of her kind.
拥有火联最先进的武器
The finest weapon of the URM Technarchy.
我要你帮我消灭阿丽塔
I need you to destroy this Alita.
把她 的心脏带给我
I need you to bring me her heart.
不杀死她   誓不罢休
I live only for her death.
我讨厌他这么做
I hate when he does that.
他不是一个能容忍失败的家伙
This is not a man who tolerates failure.
我不会把自己前途交给一堆废铁
I'm not trusting my future to a piece of iron.
你有什么打算
What do you have in mind?
敬梦想
To dreams.
我喜欢你的劲头
I like your drive, Hugo.
你跟着我的团队很有前途
You have a solid future with my team.
我的未来属于撒冷
My future's in Zalem.
我每天都记得你的承诺
I remember your promise every day.
赚够一百万
To send me up.
你就会把我送上去
When I get you a million credits.
个人而言
Personally...
我是宁可做鸡头  也不想做凤尾
I'd rather rule in hell than serve in heaven.
在上面我们是食物链最低端
We'd be at the bottom of the food chain up there,
而在下面
but down here...
我们就是王者
we can live like kings.
那么
So...
给我讲一讲你的朋友吧
Tell me about this friend of yours.
阿丽塔？
Alita?
不错的名字
Is that her name?
阿丽塔
Alita. Hmm.
早上好
Hi.
你这是怎么了
What happened to you?
昨晚和维克托聊到很晚
I wound up hanging out with Vector.
我们还一起喝了点酒
Some alcohol was involved.
很明显
Apparently.
所以维克托
So, Vector?
就是你和撒冷之间的联系
Is that your connection for getting into Zalem?
是
Yeah.
Oh.
我还希望你能留在这里
I was hoping maybe you'd wanna stay.
是   不是马上走
Hey, it's not right away.
我还没有挣到足够的钱
I still gotta raise the rest of the money first.
没事的
It's okay.
这是你的梦想
It's your dream.
我知道你一直想上去
I know it's what you've always wanted.
知道吗
You know...
我一直都很笃定
I was always so sure.
但自从你出现
Now you come along...
我就动摇了
nothing's clear anymore.
你还要挣多少钱才能上去
How much more do you need before you can go?
9万
90k.
9万?
90k?
我可以去赚赏金
I can make that in bounties.
我去找
I'll just figure out who has
悬赏最高的人
the highest prices on their heads...
然后除掉他们
and then I'll take them out.
不  我不能让你这么做
No, I can't ask you to do that for me.
为了你我愿意做任何事
I'd do whatever I had to for you.
甚至愿意付出一切
I'd give you whatever I have.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
把我的心给你
I'd give you my heart.
拿着
Take it.
它由火联的微型反应堆驱动
It's got an URM Micro-Reactor for a power supply,
也许值好几百万
probably worth millions.
动用你的关系找一个买家
With your connections, you can find a buyer...
就能赚够钱把我们都送上去
you could make enough for both of us to go to Zalem...
然后找个便宜的地方
and then we just find a cheap replacement...
不  不行
No.
别这样   你一直在买卖零件啊
Come on, you buy and sell parts all day long.
不要无缘无故为人付出
Don't just do things for people.
不管你认为他们有多善良
No matter how good you think they are,
或者多值得
or how deserving they are.
我只知道全力付出
It's all or nothing with me.
这样才是我
This is who I am.
我知道
I know.
没事的
It's okay.
放回去
Put it back.
我刚是不是很夸张
That was pretty intense, huh?
是啊  非常夸张
Yeah, that was very intense.
抱歉
Sorry.
也许还有别的方法
Maybe there's another way.
维克托想让你去次级联盟试训
Vector wants you to try out for Second League.
什么
What?
你可以成为机动球明星
You become a big Motorball star,
然后赚一大笔钱
make a pile of money...
我们就能一起上去
we can go to Zalem together.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
我可当不了职业球员
I can't be a pro Motorball player.
阿丽
Ali...
你绝对是冠军
you could be a champion.
如果试训获胜
You win this tryout...
所有球探都会抢着要你
every scout will be killing each other to get to you.
我们能免费上去
We'll be home free.
除非你当我教练
Only if you'll be my coach.
有必要的话
Well, if that's what it takes.
很有必要
That's what it takes.
你要杀了她
Are you going to kill her?
不
No.
比那还狠
Much worse.
依德  你说人类能爱上改造人吗
Ido, can a human love a cyborg?
怎么
Why?
这个改造人爱上人类了
Does this cyborg love a human?
嗯.....
Mm-hmm.
人类可以爱上改造人
A human can love a cyborg...
不过  你得先专心比赛  阿丽塔
but you have to keep your mind on the game, Alita.
场上的争夺肯定十分激烈
It can get very rough out there.
哪怕 只是试训
Even for a tryout.
试试这个
Try these.
你专门为我做的
Did you make these for me?
没错
Yes.
它们不会让你变快  有规则限制
They won't make you any faster. It's regulation.
但也不会拖后腿
But at least they won't fail you.
我们约好
Here's our deal.
你一会进去比赛
You go in there, you race,
取胜  然后回到这儿
you win, you come back right here.
把这些护板都戴好   尤其是这个
You wear all of these pads, especially this one.
我不需要这些东西
I don't need all this crap.
不  你需要
Yes, you do.
记住
Remember...
如果你弄坏了这个身体  我是修不好的
if you wreck this body, I can't fix it.
- 这可是火联科技- 我知道了
- This is URM technology. - Yes, I know.
找个地方看比赛吧
Now, go find a place to watch,
你弄得我都紧张了
because you're making me nervous.
祝你好运
Good luck.
回头见
Bye.
感谢各位能前来救急
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
你们都是这项赛事的败类
You are the scum of the game.
但今晚   你们是我钦点的
But tonight, you are handpicked scum.
因为这不是一场比赛
Because tonight is not a game.
而是一次猎杀
It is a hunt.
我会奖赏50万元
I'm paying 500,000...
只要有人杀死那个叫阿丽塔的女孩
to the one who kills the girl called Alita.
嗨
Hey.
你在哪儿  试训马上就开始了
Where are you? The tryout's about to start.
我在路上了
I'm on my way.
还要先去办点事
There's something I've gotta do first.
这是为了我们   记得吗
I'm doing this for us, remember?
你可别错过
You can't miss it.
不会的   相信我
I won't. Trust me.
求你了   快住手
Please, just stop.
我没有伤害过你们
I didn't do anything to you.
这只是生意   不是针对你
It's just business. Nothing personal.
丹治  住手
Tanji, stop!
你叫我名字?
Using my name?
你是怎么回事
Man, what's wrong with you?
我做不下去了
I can't do this anymore.
怎么了  最近你基本都不露面
What's the matter? You're already gone half the time.
现在又来跟我废话
Now you show up with this line of crap!
为了你那机器女朋友
It's the little hardbody, isn't it?
听着   都结束了  你明白吗
Listen, it's over. Do you understand?
我不干了
I'm out.
如果你还有脑子   你也该收手
And if you had any brains, you'd leave this behind, too.
我退出
I'm out.
永远
For good.
你就该拆了那个贱人
You should've jacked that bitch when you had the chance.
也许那样就能上去
Would've been on your way to Zalem right now.
真是非常专业
Well, very professional.
我们不想惹麻烦
Hey, man, we don't want any trouble.
如果他是你的猎物  抱歉  归你了
If this is your mark, we're sorry. He's all yours.
雨果
Hugo.
拆解改造人
Jacking cyborgs.
你的小女友怕是会多心
Your little girlfriend might take that
你觉得呢
kind of personally, don't you think?
嗯?
Hmm?
你也懂姑娘的
But you know girls.
也许她会哭着原谅你呢
She'll probably get all weepy and forgive you...
当他看到你的头
when I show her your head.
根本没有对我的悬赏
There's no marker out on me.
会有的
There will be.
杀人犯都是会有悬赏的
Murder pulls a tight little bounty...
哪怕是你这样的垃圾
even with gutter trash like you.
我从来没有杀过人
I never killed anyone.
这就杀过了
You just did.
她以为可以瞧不起我
She thinks she can punk me, huh?
雨果  快跑
Hugo, run!
接下来进行次级联盟试训
Next up is Second League tryouts.
现在有请工厂代表队前往起跑线
Will the Factory practice team report to the line?
今晚的胜利者将离获取冠军联盟的参赛资格
The winner tonight will make it one step closer...
更进一步
to qualifying for the Champions League.
今晚的选手来者不善
Well, that is one tough lineup.
一定会是场激烈的比赛
This is gonna be one heck of a match tonight.
那不是工厂的球队
That's no Factory team.
什么
What?
后排的两个家伙
These two punks in the back...
身上带着悬赏的标记
there are bounty markers on them.
而其他人  都是猎人勇士
And the other guys, they are Hunter-Warriors.
下面有请今晚参加试训的一名新人
And here comes tonight's one new prospect.
好了  伙计们  为阿丽塔鼓掌加油吧
Okay, then, folks, give it up for Alita!
雨果把她送上门了
Hugo brought her right to us.
- 你承诺他什么了- 嗯...
- What'd you promise him? - Hmm.
当然是送他去撒冷
I'm sending him to Zalem, of course.
阿丽塔! 阿丽塔!
Alita! Alita!
嗨
Hey.
以为今天现场只有一个新人
Since there is only one new prospect...
所以将不会有团队战
- What's up? - ...there will be no teams.
今晚我们将进行割喉战
The name of the game is Cut-throat.
下手别太狠   伙计们
Go easy on me, guys.
当然   孩子
Sure, kid.
别担心
No worries.
- 阿丽塔- 你在做什么
- Alita! - What are you doing?
这是个圈套   你必须离开
It's a setup. You gotta get outta there.
他们要杀了你
They're gonna kill you!
到底是谁
Which ones?
他们都是
All of them!
选手们   十秒倒计时
Players, 10-second warning.
五秒倒计时
Five seconds...
新人阿丽塔
The new kid, Alita,
在一开圈就抢占先机拿到球
takes possession right off the snap.
无聊的周二晚突然变得比季后赛还刺激
A slow Tuesday night just got hotter than the playoffs.
看来观众朋友们都迷上了
Looks like the fans have themselves
这位新的挑战者
an underdog darling...
她有天使的面孔和为战场而生的身躯
with the face of an angel and a body built for battle.
看来这场球赛
Maybe a little Motorball
将会演变成一场战斗
will break out in the middle of this fight.
真该死
Oh, crap.
噢   快看  观众朋友们
Oh! Looks like it's
现在他们开始无差别攻击了
"No rules Tuesday" out there, folks.
Ouch!这下肯定疼死了
Ouch! You know that hurts!
钢针给阿丽塔造成了不少麻烦
Stinger's got Alita in a lot of trouble.
她一定在更衣室里
She must've said something in the locker room
跟这帮家伙说了不怎么中听的话
that these guys did not like.
99号选手
Number 99...
阿丽塔
Alita!
阿丽   是我
Ali, it's me.
我遇上麻烦了
I've got a big problem.
雨果   现在可不是好时候
Hugo, this is not a good time.
他想要杀了我
He's trying to kill me.
谁想杀了你
Who's trying to kill you?
扎潘   那个猎人勇士
Zapan, the Hunter-Warrior.
他杀了丹治
He killed Tanji.
怎么回事
What do you mean?
现在他来抓我了
Now, he's coming for me.
不知道们的战斗天使
Not sure our Battle Angel
能不能突破重围
can get out of this one.
见鬼   他追上来了
Oh, shit. Here he comes!
你在哪
Where are you?
我准备去老教堂
I'm headed to the old church.
好的  我来了
Okay. I'm coming.
难以置信   太刺激了
I can't believe it! Incredible!
我从未见过这样的比赛
I've never seen anything like this.
我马上就到
Hey, I'm almost there.
收到
Got it.
看你往哪跑
Where are you going, huh?
看来你的小男友对你隐瞒了不少事情
Looks like your Hugo hasn't been entirely honest with you.
那是真的吗
Is it true?
阿丽
Ali...
你  你不明白
you don't understand.
我从未杀过任何人
I never killed anyone.
我们只是拆解零件
We only jacked parts.
我们打晕他们  然后抢劫  仅此而已
We paralyzed them and stripped them, that's all.
我得攒钱去撒冷
I needed the money for Zalem.
闪开  让我完成工作
Step aside and let me do my job.
你再敢碰他   我就杀了你
Touch him again and I will kill you.
阻止
Interference between
一个持证猎手猎杀其目标
a licensed Hunter-Warrior and his kill...
这样的行为违反了工厂法律还有猎人守则
is a violation of Factory Law and the Hunter's Code.
他是我的
He's mine!
那你杀了他
Then make the kill.
动手吧  猎人勇士
Come on, Hunter-Warrior.
今晚  你会成为我们的一员
Tonight, you become one of us.
嗯 嗯
Mm-mmm.
要知道   猎人守则里
You know, there's no room for love or mercy
可没有爱情仁慈一说
in the Hunter's Code.
那我帮你一把好了
Let me make it easier for you.
雨果
Hugo!
清交付犯罪雨果  悬赏编号9107
Deliver the criminal Hugo, Bounty 9107.
此人犯了谋杀罪
Wanted for the crime of murder.
你最好在我们之前下手
You better finish him before we do!
这是猎人守则
It's Hunter Law!
我得带你去找依德
I have to get you to Ido.
不  百夫长还在
No. Centurions.
如果出去时我还活着
If you go back out there with me alive,
我们两都得死
they'll kill us both.
你做了什么   你做了什么
What did you do? What did you do?
我没有杀那个人
I didn't kill that guy.
不过有什么关系呢
But what does it matter?
我肢解了那些人
I tore people apart.
和你一样的人   为了钱
People like you, for money.
你今晚做了什么
Where were you tonight?
我去组织其他人了
I went to go stop the others.
- 告诉他们我退出- 为什么
- And tell them I quit. - Why?
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
我很抱歉
God, I'm sorry.
找到他们了吗
Did you find them?
没有
No.
他们跑了
They're gone.
你好冰啊  千万不要死
You're so cold. Please don't die.
千万不要死
Please don't.
我愿意用我的生命救活他
I'd give him my life if I could.
也许你可以
Maybe you can.
你包庇悬赏中的犯人
You have violated Factory Law and the Hunter's Code
违反了工厂法律的猎人守则
by protecting a wanted felon.
罪犯雨果在哪  悬赏编号9107
Where is the criminal Hugo, Bounty 9107?
雨果已经死了
Hugo is dead.
我来领赏金
I claim the bounty.
猎人勇士36651号
Hunter-Warrior 26651.
确认击杀
Claim confirmed.
Ah.
这把戏玩的不错
Yeah, that's a cute trick.
你认为这能行得痛吗
You think this is gonna work, huh? Hmm?
把他交给我
Give me that.
违规
Violation.
猎人勇士扎潘
Hunter-Warrior Zapan...
夺取他人猎物
stealing another's bounty
违反了工厂法律一级猎人守则
is against Factory Law and the Hunter's Code.
谢了
Thanks.
我的脸
My face.
My... My face!
我的脸
My face!
不
No!
他怎么样了
How is he?
这座城市能让好人都变坏
This city corrupts even good people.
他很好
He's good.
情况稳定
He's stable.
依莲的手术技术太高明了
Chiren's surgical technique was brilliant.
脑部没有任何损伤
There's no brain damage.
维克托就是在骗人
Vector was running a scam.
如果你身在地面  就只能留在下面
If you're born on the ground, you stay on the ground...
不管你花多少钱都一样
and no amount of money can change that.
唯一可以从地面去往撒冷的方法
The only one way to get from the lower world to Zalem...
就是成为最终冠军
is to become Final Champion.
是不可能花钱上去的
You can't buy your way up there.
你怎么知道得这么清楚
But how do you know that for sure?
我生在那里
I was born there.
我把自己额头上的撒冷印记磨掉了
I've removed it myself, the Mark of Zalem.
因为我们的女儿生病
With our daughter's illness,
依莲和我被上面的人流放到钢铁城
Chiren and I were forced to descend here to Iron City.
而负责流放我们的人就是
And the man responsible for our exile...
在背后监控一切的人
the watcher behind the eyes...
诺瓦
is Nova.
你都拿到了她的心脏
You had her heart in your hands...
却没有杀了她
and you let her live.
- 是的- 为什么
- I did. - Why?
因为我是个医生
Because I'm a doctor.
同时
And...
也是个母亲
I'm a mother.
我曾经忘记了这一点
And somehow I forgot that.
我做不下去了
I can't do this anymore.
我退出
I'm out.
依莲  等等
Chiren, wait.
不觉得是时候回去了吗
Don't you think it's time you went to Zalem?
我现在就可以把你送上去
I could send you up there right now.
我想要的
What I want...
并不在上面
it isn't up there.
我要去做一件事
I have to do something.
你要等着我
I'll come back for you.
这是我的错
This is my fault.
都是我的错
永远不要责怪你自己
Don't ever feel sorry for yourself.
你就是为战斗而生的
You're the only one built for this.
谢谢你  爸爸
Thank you, Father.
维克托
Vector!
检测到攻击意图
Hostile intention detected.
放下你的武器
Surrender your weapon.
安保报告
Security report.
警告   警告
Violation! Violation!
抓到她了吗
Did you get her?
安保
Security?
你根本没想送雨果去撒冷  对不对
You were never going to send Hugo to Zalem, were you?
哇，哇，哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
我一直都是信守承诺的
I always keep my promise to send people up.
比如依莲医生
Like Dr. Chiren here.
诺瓦需要器官进行实验
Nova demands body parts for his experiments.
尤其他喜欢的那些人的大脑
Especially, the brains of people he admires.
这也是这些人上去撒冷的唯一方法
And that is the only way anyone ever gets to Zalem.
我等你好久了
It took you long enough.
我就知道你不会坐以待毙的
I knew you wouldn't wait for your fate
小跳蚤
to find you, little flea.
起来
Get up.
防御环来了
Defense Ring!
要完成任务
Finish the mission.
毁掉撒冷
Destroy Zalem.
我知道敌人是谁了
I know who my enemy is.
他此刻正看着我们
And I know he's watching us now.
你只不过是个奴隶
And you're just his slave.
我也只是个不起眼的女孩
And I'm just an insignificant girl.
说话
Speak.
不  不  不  等等
No. No. No. Wait.
说话
Speak!
你想让我说什么  我都听你的
What do you want me to say? I will say anything.
没问你
Not you.
是他
Him!
终于见面了   阿丽塔
So we finally meet, Alita.
当然不是你的名字
Not your real name, of course.
诺瓦
Nova?
你在哪
Where are you?
家里  此时此刻
Home. As we speak.
头顶上
Feet up.
小姑娘
Well, my girl,
你大大超出了我的预期
you've certainly exceeded my expectations.
杀了我的勇士格鲁依什卡
Killing my champion Grewishka.
更令我惊讶的是
Most impressive.
还改变了依莲这么自私的人
And turning a selfish creature like Chiren.
我确实没想到
I didn't see that coming.
所以你从这儿出去时  工厂也不会再去
So, when you walk out of here, the Factory won't stop you.
阻止你
This time.
我能否活命你说了不算
I don't need your permission to live.
有人未必
Others might.
以你的依德博士为例
Your Dr. Ido, for example.
还有雨果呢
And what about Hugo?
他还活着  对吧
He's still alive, isn't he?
我们会追杀他
We will track him down.
嗯...
Hmm.
我发现   永生的唯一乐趣
I've found the only way to enjoy immortality...
就是看着其他人死去
is to watch others die.
你刚失去了一个傀儡
You just lost a puppet.
看起来会死啊
Well, that looks fatal.
不过没关系
No matter.
维克托早就厌烦了
Vector was getting tiresome.
你犯了这辈子最大的错误
You've made the biggest mistake of your life.
是什么
And what's that?
就是低估了我这个人
Underestimating who I am.
我们下次再会
Then until next time.
你记住
Remember.
我能看到一切
I see everything.
阿丽塔
Alita.
工厂的人过来找雨果了
Factory enforcers came looking for Hugo.
不清楚是怎么知道他还活着的
Somehow they knew he'd been kept alive.
我帮他逃跑了  但现在全城封锁
I helped him escape, but they've sealed the city.
- 他们要找到他- =他现在在哪
- They're going to find him. - Where is he?
他想去上面
He's trying to go up.
雨果
Hugo!
Hugo.
雨果
Hugo!
站住
Stop.
你必须下来  我们不能呆在这
You have to come down. We can't stay up here.
我被悬赏了   这是唯一的方法
There's a bounty on me. This is the only way.
不  这太危险了  我们必须马上下去
No, this is dangerous. We have to get down, now.
如果我回去   我会死
If I go back down there, I'm dead.
不   你必须听我说  好吗
No. You have to listen to me, okay?
我以前就来过这儿
I've been right here before.
这正是诺瓦希望你来的地方
This is exactly where Nova wants you.
他想利用你杀了我
He's using you to get to me.
来吧  我们一起下去
Come on, we have to go back down.
我们属于那里   阿丽塔
We belong up there, Alita.
我们不属于任何地方  除了彼此身边
We don't belong anywhere except together.
我们要逃一辈子
You'll always be running.
一起逃
Together.
跟我走吧
Come with me.
求你了
Please.
我们会自由的
We could be free.
好吧
Okay.
不
No!
抓紧
Hold on.
握爪到你了
I got you.
好了好了   不要动
Okay, okay. Don't move.
不要动
Don't move.
我慢慢把你拉上来
I'm gonna lift you up slowly.
谢谢你
Thank you...
拯救了我
for saving me.
我爱你
I love you.
不
No!
她只花了几个月时间
It took her only a few months...
就从次级联盟脱颖而出
to rise through the ranks of the Second League.
在今晚   她也将完成
And tonight, she makes her first appearance
自己在冠军联盟的首秀
in the Champions League.
她将有机会争夺最终比赛的冠军
Where she has a chance at becoming Final Champion...
并前往撒冷
and going to Zalem.
阿丽塔! 阿丽塔! 阿丽塔!
Alita! Alita! Alita!
下面让我们有请伟大的战斗天使
Let's hear it for the Battle Angel herself...
99号选手
number 99...
阿丽塔
Alita!
阿丽塔! 阿丽塔! 阿丽塔!
Alita! Alita! Alita!